# Ganzorig Erdenebat

https://rozig.me

Email: the.ganzorig25@gmail.com LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/rozig/

### Summary

Accomplished full-stack developer with 2 years of experience playing key role in development, deployment, and support of enterprise-level software. Strong technical skills, with hands-on experience in both front-end and backend development using Django and Angular web frameworks. Personable team player with talent for collaborating with diverse technical teams. Experience successfully implementing projects with web services, design patterns and latest frameworks.

#### **EDUCATION**

## Maharishi University of Management

Fairfield, IA

Master of Science in Computer Science; GPA: 4.00

Oct. 2017 - Present

Address: Miami, FL 33130

Mobile: +1 (312) 404-1266

Mongolian University of Science and Technology

Ulaanbaatar, Mongolia

Bachelor of Science in Software Engineering; GPA: 3.46

Aug. 2013 - Jan. 2017

#### EXPERIENCE

Genius Plaza Inc. Back-end Developer

Miami, FL

Aug. 2018 - Present

Infinite Solutions LLC

Ulaanbaatar, Mongolia Jun. 2016 - Nov. 2017

Full Stack Developer

- - o Transfer: Transfer is a fintech solution for receiving and sending money over the world. Worked on core system, API services and front-end development.
  - Mobicom Branded Application: Managed back-end server for Mobicom Branded Application. Performed backend development, API services development, testing and maintenance and database design.
  - o Golds Gym Website: Developed official website for Golds Gym Mongolia. Conducted unit testing and maintenance. Performed front-end and back-end development.
  - ArigBank: In-charge of maintenance and front-end development.

#### Projects

- Online Publication Platform: Clone of Medium.com, built RESTful API Services for front-end use and implemented authentication with JWT (JSON Web Token). Developed on MEAN Stack (MongoDB, ExpressJS, Angular 5, NodeJS) using Sublime Text, Git, Terminal, NPM, Amazon S3, and Google Cloud Platform.
- Mumagram: Developed Instagram-like web application for MUM students using Java Servlet for back-end, JSP with UI-Kit and jQuery for front-end development, MySQL for database. Used Sublime Text, Git, Terminal, Bower, Amazon S3, Google Cloud Platform and Maven.
- Online Banking Application: Developed web application that allows user to transfer money and manage accounts. Used Spring for back-end, Angular 5 for front-end development and MySQL for database. Used tools are Sublime Text, Git, Terminal and Maven.
- Nutrition Calculator: Developed nutrition calculation web application on Diango (Python); created HTML templates using Bootstrap. Used PostgreSQL for database and Django ORM for mapping. Used Sublime Text, Anaconda, Terminal
- Logistics System: Developed web application for cargo delivery service on Django (Python). Created HTML templates using Bootstrap and used PostgreSQL for database and Django ORM for mapping. Used Sublime Text, pip, Terminal and Git.

## Programming Skills

• Languages: Python, PHP, JavaScript, TypeScript, Bash, SQL SDLC: Agile/SCRUM, RUP, Waterfall

• Web: jQuery, CSS3/HTML5, SASS, Express Frameworks: Django, Symfony, NodeJS, Angular 2/4/5

• Web/App Servers: Nginx, Apache2, Node Databases: MySQL, PostgreSQL, MongoDB, SQLAlchemy • Design Patterns: Factory Method, Singleton, Adapter, MVC Web Services: RESTful, Django REST